http://www.hmts.com/privacy-policy

Home Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyPolicy StatementProtecting your privacy is important to DISA Global Solutions, Inc. (“DISA”). The following policy conveys how DISA uses and safeguards the personal information you provide on the DISA corporate web site and related DISA services.Information CollectionWhen you browse to the DISA corporate web site, you do so anonymously. Personal information — including your email address — is not collected.Some of our corporate web pages utilize "cookies." Cookies are identifiers which a web site can send to your browser and are kept on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you.Finally, there are times that we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your email address, and possibly your postal address, for purposes such as correspondence, registration, or participation in an online survey. We will not share any of this information with any third party without your express written consent and will take reasonable steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure.Information UseAny and all information collected at this site will be kept confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed without your express written consent.If you provide us with your email address, or have done so in the past, we may upon occasion send you email offers, or advise you of updates to the system. We may use information you have given us, for example, to provide a service, measure consumer interest in our various services, or inform you about new products and services.Personal Information Disclosure: United States or Overseas Personal information submitted to DISA for a background screening investigation may at times be transferred outside of the United States. All personal information will be transmitted and stored in a secure manner in accordance with the terms of this policy as DISA has taken measures to protect personal and confidential data:a. Documentation or information such as passport numbers, or unique identification numbers and date of birth, are not sent to anyone overseas other than the actual verification provider (e.g. employer or school registrar) whenever possible.b. Where it is necessary to utilize a local firm, the local firm will first be asked to provide local contact information so that the CRA can contact the foreign verifying party directly.c. If, due to infrastructure or other issues in a foreign country, a foreign research firm must perform the verification, then DISA or our agent has properly vetted the local firm and will redact any unnecessary information.Privacy, Choice, and Opting OutDISA respects the privacy of the individuals and clients who are the subjects of DISA Services, including but not limited to background checks. DISA will collect, store, and use confidential information following best practices and also in compliance with applicable law, including the FCRA.Links to Other SitesDISA is not responsible for the privacy policies, activities or web sites of third parties, such as advertisers, content providers and Alliance Partners. This policy does not cover the information practices of those third parties. We suggest that you contact the relevant parties or access their online policies directly for information about their data collection.Event RegistrationDISA event registration forms require users to give DISA contact information (such as a name and email address), and other information (for instance, a job title or role). We may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about the event. The customer’s contact information may also be used to contact the visitor when necessary about the event. In some cases, the contact information may be shared with event sponsors and other attendees to foster collaboration.Privacy of ChildrenThe DISA corporate web site and the related DISA services are designed to be used solely by companies and individuals for business purposes. Therefore, DISA does not anticipate that anyone under the age of 18 will access or use our corporate web site or services. DISA will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under the age of 18.Acceptance of TermsBy using this site, you signify your consent to DISA that you agree to this policy. DISA reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of DISA corporate web site and related services following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact:DISA Global Solutions, Inc.Attn: Privacy Officer10900 Corporate Centre Drive, Ste. 250Houston, TX 77041281-673-2400Email: InfoSec@disa.comIn accordance with California Civil Code 1786.20, in order to obtain additional information about DISA's policies and practices in connection with background screening investigations, please contact DISA's Director of Background Compliance, Morgan Reynolds by any of the following means:Email: morgan.reynolds@disa.comAddress: 17592 E. 17th Street, Suite 300, Tustin, CA 92780Phone: 714-669-4835
Subscribe
DISA Global Solutions10900 Corporate Centre Drive Ste. 250Houston,
DISA Global Solutions. All rights reserved.
